const STORE = {
    questions: [ //1
        {
            question: "How many times has Robert Downey Jr. played Iron Man?",
            options: [
                "3",
                "9",
                "7",
                "10"
            ],
            answer: "10"
        },
        //2
        {
            question: "Who is the brother to Wanda Maximoff aka Scarlet Witch?",
            options: [
                "Wolverine",
                "Quicksilver",
                "Doctor Strange",
                "Hawkeye"
            ],
            answer: "Quicksilver"
        },
        //3
        {
            question: "Where is Wakanda located?",
            options: [
                "Australia",
                "Europe",
                "Africa",
                "South America"
            ],
            answer: "Africa"
        },
        //4
        {
            question: "Who has made an appearance in almost every Marvel movie?",
            options: [
                "Stan Lee",
                "Tony Stark",
                "Jack Kirby",
                "Thanos"
            ],
            answer: "Stan Lee"
        },
        //5
        {
            question: "What is the name of the main villain in the second Avengers film?",
            options: [
                "Thanos",
                "Ultron",
                "The Collector",
                "Green Goblin"
            ],
            answer: "Ultron"
        },
        //6
        {
            question: "Who directed Thor (2011)?",
            options: [
                "Jon Favreau",
                "Ron Howard",
                "Kenneth Branagh",
                "Steven Spielberg"
            ],
            answer: "Kenneth Branagh"
        },
        //7
        {
            question: 'In which film did Hawkey first appear?',
            options: [
                "The Avengers",
                "The Incredible Hulk",
                "Iron Man 2",
                "Thor"
            ],
            answer: "Thor"
        },
        //8
        {
            question: "Who is Black Panther’s sister?",
            options: [
                "Ramonda",
                "Shuri",
                "Ororo",
                "Nehanda"
            ],
            answer: "Shuri"
        },
        //9
        {
            question: "This person is second in command of S.H.I.E.L.D. in The Avengers.",
            options: [
                "Phil Coulson",
                "Maria Hill",
                "Nick Fury",
                "Clint Barton"
            ],
            answer: "Maria Hill"
        },
        //10
        {
            question: "What part of Thor’s body does he lose in Thor: Ragnarok?",
            options: [
                "Eye",
                "Arm",
                "Leg",
                "Foot"
            ],
            answer: "Eye"
        },

    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    score: 0
};